Universal Negro Improvement Association records, 1921-1989
Emory University
- Other organizations, 1921-1989, Series 6; Box 23-24; OP 4-8
  - Cronon, E. David, Black Moses, book advertisement (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Davis, S. A., "Author and interpreter of Biblical predictions as they apply to the black and white race," various printed, no date (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Davis, William, funeral program, Four Mile Baptist Church (New Ellenton, South Carolina), 1989 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Detroit Civic Rights Committee, open letter to Councilmen of the City of Detroit, July 19, 1935 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Faith Tabernacle Baptist Church (Mutchmore Memorial) (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), broadside for fashion show, March 14, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Friends for Independence of Namibia, flyer, no date (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Garvey Club (New York, New York), records, 1938, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Garvey International Library and Educational Institution (New York, New York), broadside to grand opening, August 16, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Garvey Memorial Foundation (Detroit, Michigan), minutes, March 4-5, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - George VI Memorial Park (Kingston, Jamaica), programme for unveiling of Marcus Garvey bust, November 4, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Ghana, various brochures (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Ghana Independence Day, Parking passes, March 1957 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Ghana Students Association of the USA and Canada, reception program, July 29, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Greater Detroit Youth Assembly, Newsletter, Vol. 1, No. 1, January 15, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - House of Knowledge (Chicago, Illinois), advertising cards, no date (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Institute of Black Nationalists, flyer, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - International African Students Aid Association, program, July 18, 1923 (Box OP6)
  - International Committee on African Affairs (New York, New York), brochure, no date (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - International Committee of Young Men's Christian Association, brochure, no date (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - The Jolly Handicap Club (Detroit, Michigan), raffle ticket, November 20, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Kongo University Committee of One Hundred, invitation, July 1, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Liberty Building and Trading Company, stock certificate, 1927-1928 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Marcus Garvey Memorial Educational Foundation (Brooklyn, New York), brochure, no date (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Marcus Garvey Elementary School (Chicago, Illinois), dedication program, October 4, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Marcus Garvey School for African Education: Instructor's Guide, no date (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Maryland Petition Committee, MPC Bulletin, January 1957 (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Michigan Committee for Academic Freedom, "Without Fear or Favor: The Case of the Michigan Students," September 1940 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - The National Christian Liberty Front of America (Washington, D.C.), brochure, "The Coming Liberation of America," no date (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - National Institute for Negro Advancement, Constitution, no date (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - National Negro Alliance, Constitution and Bylaws (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - National Negro Congress, various, circa 1945 (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - National Negro Labor Council (Detroit, Michigan), brochure, "Therefore, be it resolved...to end discrimination in the railroad industry," 1953 (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - National Negro Scholarship Plan, flyer, no date [Melvin Allen, organizer-director] (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - "Negro Masses Lack Government," broadside, no date (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Negro Nationalist Society of America, brochure, no date (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Negro Protective Association (Cincinnati, Ohio), broadside for mass meeting re Emmett Till, November 13, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Negro Protective Association (Cincinnati, Ohio), membership card (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Nigerian Students Union, ANAM and African Jazz-Art Society Studios (Harlem, New York), broadside for Black Solidarity Festival, March 28, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 70)
  - Philadelphia Fellowship Commission, flyer, no date (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Prince Hall Masonic Temple (Detroit, Michigan), Breakfast Dance, advertising card, June 4, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Republican National Committee, "Where Lies the Real Danger to Our Freedom and Liberties," by Emmett J. Scott, press release, June 12, 1941 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Self Determination Committee (Los Angeles, California), flyers, 1960s-1970s (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - South African Committee for Youth Work (Chicago, Illinois), program for Town Hall Meeting, December 7, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - "St. Ann's Motion, An original musical production based on James G. Spady's Marcus Garvey, African and the UNIA," poster, 1987 (Box OP7)
  - Strong, Bill, sketch of Marcus Garvey (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Thornhill, R.D. (Rev.), Finite Infinite Mentalist and Consultant, New York, New York, business card, no date (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Union Better Life Gospel Campaign of the Community Churches (Chicago, Illinois), pledge card, no date (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - United African Nationalist Movement, Unit 2 (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), conference agenda, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - United African Nationalist Movement (New York, New York), broadside for Marcus Garvey Day celebration, August 1, 1953 (Box OP8)
  - United Associates (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), directory advertisement, no date (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - United Nations, brochure, "Out Rights as Human Beings," 1951 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - United Nations, Ad Hoc Committee on Slavery, circulars, "Questionnaires on Slavery and Servitude," 1950 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - United Negro Progressive Association, brochure, no date (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - United States Congress, House Concurrent Resolution 159, June 5, 1985, regarding Marcus Garvey pardon (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - United States Constitution Council, various printed, 1970s (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Universal African Nationalist Movement, 1953-1956 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - [Unknown organization], Aims and objects (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - White America Society (Richmond, Virginia), brochure, "Abraham Lincoln: His Efforts to Make America a White Nation," no date (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - YM YWHA (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), broadside for Spring Peach Forum, May 22, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Young Afro-Americans of South Philadelphia, flyer, no date (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - YWCA (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania), broadside for mass meeting, March 31, 1946 [Andronicus Jacobs speaker] (Box 24, Folder 21)